[
  {
    "category": "Entertainment Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the name of the hero in the 80 sanimated video game 7Dragon7sLair7F",
    "correct_answer": "Dirkthe Daring",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur", "SirTobyBelch", "Guy of Gisbourne"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Animals",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the scientific name for modern day humans",
    "correct_answer": "Homo Sapiens",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Homo Ergaster",
      "Homo Erectus",
      "Homo Neanderthalensis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment%3ABooks",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is RonWeasley 7s middlename",
    "correct_answer": "Bilius",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur", "John", "Dominic"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment%3AComics",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the creator of the comicse ries2 The Walking Dead 23",
    "correct_answer": "Robert Kirkman",
    "incorrect_answers": ["StanLee", "MalcolmWheeler-Nicholson", "Robert Crumb"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment ABoardGames",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Atthestarto fastandar dgame of the Monopoly Cif youth rowadoub lesixCwhichs quarewouldy oulandon",
    "correct_answer": "Electric Company",
    "incorrect_answers": ["WaterWorks", "Chance", "CommunityChest"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the capital of Jamaica ",
    "correct_answer": "Kingston",
    "incorrect_answers": ["RiodeJaneiro", "DaresSalaam", "Kano"]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "When did Jamaica recieve its independence from England ",
    "correct_answer": "1962",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1492", "1963", "1987"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Animals",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Kangaroo skeep food in the irpouches next to the irchildren.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "category": "GeneralKnowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In 2013 how much money was lost by Nigerians cams",
    "correct_answer": "412.7Billion",
    "incorrect_answers": ["495Million", "4956Million", "42.7Billion"]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Howold was LyndonB.John son when hea ssumed the role of President of the United States",
    "correct_answer": "55",
    "incorrect_answers": ["50", "60", "54"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment A VideoGames",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In World of War craft loreCwho organized the creation of the Paladins",
    "correct_answer": "Alonsus Faol",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Uther the Light bringer",
      "Alexand rosMograine",
      "Sargeras C The DaemonLord"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment VideoGames",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In the game 2Sub nautica Cave Crawler 2 will attack you.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment A Japanese Anime6Manga",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the name of the device that allows for in finiteenergy in the anime 2DimensionW",
    "correct_answer": "Coils",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Wires", "Collectors", "Tesla"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment VideoGames",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the name of Cream the Rabbit 7smomin the Sonic the Hedgehog series",
    "correct_answer": "Vanilla",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Peach", "Strawberry", "Mint"]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "These two countries held a commonwealth from the 16th to 18thcentury.",
    "correct_answer": "Polandand Lithuania",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Hutuand Rwanda",
      "North Korea and SouthKorea",
      "Bangladesh and Bhutan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment%3ATelevision",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which of the sevoice swasn7 tachoice for the House AIin2 The Simpsons Tree houseo fHorror2 short CHouse of Whacks",
    "correct_answer": "GeorgeClooney",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Matthew Perry", "Dennis Miller", "Pierce Brosnan"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment%3AMusic",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "From which album is the Gorillaz song C2 On Melancholy Hill featured",
    "correct_answer": "Plastic Beach",
    "incorrect_answers": ["DemonDays", "Humanz", "TheFall"]
  },
  {
    "category": "GeneralKnowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during there ferendum from September2014.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Entertainment VideoGames",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Left 4Dead Cwhich campaignhas the protagon is tsgoing through a subway in order to reachaho spital forevacuation",
    "correct_answer": "NoMercy",
    "incorrect_answers": ["SubwaySprint", "HospitalHavoc", "BloodHarvest"]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the last colony the UK cededmar king theend of the British Empire",
    "correct_answer": "HongKong",
    "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Australia", "Ireland"]
  }
]
